Track 5.3 Unit 5 Language in use Activity 1
Bài 5.3 Đơn vị 5 Ngôn ngữ sử dụng Bài tập 1
What did Ella do at her party?
Ella đã làm gì ở tiệc sinh nhật?
Listen and tick
Nghe và đánh dấu tích
Look at this photo of my birthday party!
Nhìn tấm ảnh tiệc sinh nhật của mình này!
Wow! Did you dress up as a leopard?
Wow! Bạn hóa trang thành con báo à?
No, I didn't. I was a lion.
Không. Mình là con sư tử.
Oh, OK. Did you dance with your friends?
Ồ, OK. Bạn có nhảy với bạn bè không?
Yes, I did. My grandma played the piano.
Có. Bà mình chơi piano.
Great! Did you eat pizza?
Tuyệt! Bạn có ăn pizza không?
Yes, I did. There was lots of cheese on it. It was delicious.
Có. Có rất nhiều phô mai trên đó. Rất ngon.
Did you play with dolls?
Bạn có chơi búp bê không?
No, I didn't. We didn't have time.
Không. Bọn mình không có thời gian.
Oh.
Ồ.